Meta SAMRACH



Contacts

Address: #403, NR1, Sangkat Prek Eng, Khan Chbar Ampeou, Phnom Penh,

Cambodia

Phone: (+885) 967769351

Email: metasamrach29@gmail.com

Languages Khmer-Native English-Fluent

Skills

- Organizational Management of Programs (plan, implement, evaluation, and report)
- Data-Driven Research and Analysis
- Proficient with using Microsoft Applications (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, etc.)
- Writing (notetaking, reporting, letter, developing concept note/proposal, estimate budget plan)
- Public Speaking/Facilitation (MC, trainer, facilitator, etc.)
- Effective Communication (verbal andwritten)
- Attention to detail, initiative, and output
- Effective Time Management and Organizational Skill
- Event Planning and Management (Workshop, Meeting, Seminar
- Translation, KHMER to ENGLISH (Written and Oral)

Summary

Project Assistant, with 5 years+ of experience in both government and NGO sectors. I have gained an intimate understanding of what makes technical projects successful. Experienced in the field of programme implementation with a track record of working in government sector and non-profit organizations on projects involving gender mainstreaming, youth engagement, public service delivery, poverty reduction, and good governance.

Education

2018 – 2022	Studied International Relations at Paññāsāstra University of Cambodia
2018 – 2019	Studied English Diploma of the Intensive English for Academic Purposes at Paññāsāstra Institute of Foreign Languages
2018	Graduated High School at Prek Eng High School
2014 – 2017	Studied General English Programme at New York International School Cambodia

Working Experiences

2022-Present

Promoted & Project Assistant at Transparency International Cambodia, under Greater Young Women Empowerment in Decision Making and Accountable Public Service Delivery, funded by EU

- To assist the project team to prepare and submit weekly report, quarterly, semi-annual and annual narrative and financial reports in a timely manner;
- To assist the project team in development of project work plan and periodic reports
- To assist the Programme Coordinator and relevant project staffs to keep and maintain and effective and efficient documentation and filing system particularly related to monitoring and evaluation of the project such training reports, assessment report on capacity building programme at national and sub-national level, and reports of all project activities;
- M&E and Database Management: To assist the team in designing and conducting research or survey;
- To assist the team in tracking project data (training results, outputs, outcomes, efficiency and impact), develop M&E work plan and follow up its implementation;

Reference

Available Upon

2021 – 2022 **Programme Intern at Transparency**International Cambodia, funded by USAID

- Under the direction and guidance of the Programme Officer, provide administrative and logistical support to the implementation of the Women and Youth Empowerment in Leadership (WYEL) programme
- Work closely with citizen and youth empowerment programme staffs to contribute to the successful achievement of the planned activities including the organizations of trainings, meetings, workshops, field trips, conferences, and otheradvocacycampaigns.
- Work closely with youths to coordinate and support youth-led-initiatives and ensure the delivery of the projects' objectives.
- Provide assistance and support to program staff when required
- Travel to provinces with the programme staffs for the programme activities.

<u>Core Team as a co-founder at Smart Youth of Cambodia – Phnom Penh</u>

- Design and provide technical support to Smart Youth of Cambodia to lead local initiative projects of protecting the Mangroves at Kampot province.
- Coordinate social media campaign to promote the local tourism and the mangroves.
- Manage overall logistical and documentation supports with campaign engagement and mobilization activities with youth, communities and public on promoting the mangroves project.
- Mobilize young people to raise awareness on environment protection and inspire their meaningful participation in the decision of community developments.

Academic Achievements

Aug 2021-March 2022-

I has successfully completed the training program into the Young Women Research's program, Organized by Pact Building Local Promise and University of PUTHISASTRA

and funded by USAID.

The goal of the project are to empower women researchers, to lead the research landscape in Cambodia with translational research that will inform policy and to ensure

collaboration across the sector

interdisciplinary approach (business, ICT, social science and health) leverage different perspectives/ expertise to design solutions.

Sep-Oct 2022-

I has successfully completed training program on "Young Budget Trackers for Transparency on September 29 until 04 October 2022 at Siem Reap Province, Organized by Transparency International Cambodia.

Training Courses

2022	T1 C11 1 (1 (' '
2023	I has successfully completed training program
	on " Internet freedom, digital rights, digital security,
	internet censorship monitoring by OONI Probe tools
	running and advocacy plans" from April 04-05, 2023
	in Phnom Penh, Cambodia, Organized by, Advocacy
	and Policy Institute.
May, 2022	I has successfully completed training program on
	"Investigative Reporting on Corruption" on May 05-
	07, 2022 conducted in Phnom Penh, Co-Organized by
	Cambodian Journalists Alliance (CamboJA) and
	Transparency International Cambodia.
Sept 2021-	I has successfully completed the course SHEA and
	Safeguarding on September 08, 2021. Organized by
	ActionAid international. the online course covered the
	following areas by describe why SHEA and
	Safeguarding concerns applying basic Safeguarding
	practices to ensure my work with ActionAid is safe
	and does not cause human.
Sept 2021-	I has successfully completed the online course on
	Global Platform and Youth Hub Introduction on
	September 15th 2021, Organized by GLOBAL
	PLATFORM NETWORK FOR YOUTH-LED
	ACTIVISM ActionAid.
2020	I has successfully completed a course of "THE
	METHODOLOGY OF SICENTIFIC ARTICALE
	WRITING" via online training at Mindset
	e

Development Organization.

Volunteer Experiences

April, 2021-2022	ActionAid Cambodia	International	Organization
-	department of responsibility sponsorship te message as w	er for over ten in Fundraising and spewas to provide so am in the translation well as other logistic services to our suppose to our suppose the services the services to our suppose the services to our suppose the services to our suppose the services the services to our suppose the services to our suppose the services the services to our suppose the services t	onsorship. My upport to the ns of the child tic support to
July, 2019	14 th Biennial C	Association of Geno Convention of the In Genocide Scholars	ternational